The Girl Who Escaped: The Kara Robinson Story is a thriller,
drama, crime film directed by Simone Stock.
The true story of how Kara Robinson was kidnapped, assaulted and held captive for 18 hours,
15-year-old Kara Robinson plots a daring escape from a serial killer's apartment.
Kara Robinson, played by Katie Douglas.
Debra, played by Cara Buono.
Richard Evonitz, played by Kristian Bruun.
Lt. Aaron Rowland, played by Erik Athavale.
Sgt. Bonnie Jennings, played by Lisa Marie DiGiacinto.
Jess, played by Sophia Carriere.
Richard Marc Edward Evonitz (July 29, 1963 – June 27, 2002) was an American serial killer, kidnapper, and rapist responsible for the deaths of at
least three teenage girls in Spotsylvania County, Virginia, and the abduction of Kara Robinson in Lexington County, South Carolina.
Evonitz has been suspected of other murders, and confessed other
crimes to his sister, shortly before committing suicide.
The tone is emotional and intense.